## **Robert Jones**

I am a Front-End Web Developer with a passion for web design and creativity. I am always on the lookout for opportunities to test my skills and bring my experience into a team based environment.

(270)-289-1170 Email - Portfolio Github - LinkedIn

#### **SKILLS**

Version Control, CSS3, HTML5, Tailwind CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, React JS, Rest APIs, C#, .NET, ASP.NET, SQL, MySQL, Java

#### **PROJECTS**

#### Tech-Commerce - Code: Website

- Built from scratch React Js e-commerce site
- Designed using custom CSS and HTML5/JSX
- Custom coded JSX, styled components, and functional components

#### Crypto Axios Request — Code: Website

- Built from scratch React Js Crypto API Request with axios
- Designed using Tailwind CSS
- Built using styled components and a REST API

#### Nikola Tesla Tribute Page — Code: Website

- Portrait Designed tribute page
- Designed using custom HTML5/JSX and Bootstrap
- Details important parts of Tesla's life and his contributions.

#### Library Database — Code

- Allows the user to search for available books in the library
- Built with C#, using Microsoft SQL Server.
- Uses CRUD to add, delete, update, and load data

#### ASP.NET Calculator - Code

- Built using C# and ASP.NET
- Designed using a windows form
- Uses loop, validation, and logic to solve math equations

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### MTD, Martin TN — Assembler

August 2021 - March 2022

Inspected lawn mower frames for safety and over quality.

### Rotech, Murray KY — Warehouse

April 2020 - March 2021

Filled ticket orders and kept in stock inventory.

## Walmart, Murray KY – Associate

October 2015 - November 2019

Provided Customer Service. Unloaded freight in receiving.

#### **EDUCATION**

# West Kentucky Community and Technical College, Paducah KY — A.S.

2022

**Key Courses:** 

- C# I and C# II
- Java I and Java II
- Web Design and JavaScript
- Relational Databases